Hi guys, how are you?
Yeah, I just like I like to keep the stream that a certain like a number of
No, I was already on for over six hours
so
Ah, how are we doing guys? I'll get to the link and
It doesn't kind of interesting exciting when some of that stuff has happened, you know, I think you know, I hope everyone's a good sport
You know
Okay, you're you're and number one shatter number one shatter. We'll keep going
Good morning. I'm
Relatable are you a are you easy?
That easy in there you're on
Untrackable is unrelatable. There's easy. There's the
Difficult, I don't know
There's a there's a allegedly there's
Yes, we're back. Yes, yawn. We're back
Oh, that looks so serious, okay, so that's true, and uh, we have
Hello, hello. Hi. How are you?
Oh, I'm okay. Are you mad at me?
No, well, I wasn't until you fucking put me backstage for no reason
Well, I mean it's like you know backstage they can sound like the worst place
I said, it just means I'm trying to like have big the right balance. I'm gonna show sometimes they sometimes I get a little bit
You know what I don't know lose my temper. So I I don't know. It's just I'm just trying to
Do the camera where I'm doing I'm the camera crew. It's not you're really not off the show
You're still on this. Well, you're just kind of backstage, but I brought you back, you know
I always I always bring you back. Okay, man. I mean
It's hey, you know, it's just show business, you know
It's not business. It's not personal. It's business. Well, I wasn't really left back there too long. So yeah, I'm yeah
So is that maybe how about this one? Ah?
Liz forgive him
Liz forgive him the song
Now you're supposed to sing me an apology song and then I can sing you the all-is-for-given song
Okay, well, I'm sorry
So sorry
With your heart, I don't know how this one goes. I just get neither. Good morning
Good morning boss and you a whack a whack pack. Yeah, we have the week. It's your wake pack or either we awake packets
It's like he awakens packets. It's uh, I don't know guys
We've a lot of organizations
Spreading up all around us. I think we need to eat a compound and then I'll move there together
That's gonna be the safest plan for it. We need you know, probably you know a lot of artillery
Just guessing. Okay. So vanilla dice dice tomorrow boss and via whack pack and Jeff says yes
Yeah, I know guys I do I do we need to buy some land somewhere before Bill Gates buys it all and
You know
It won't be it won't necessarily be a sex compound. You know, I mean, you know, you guys
know
I'll be a normal cult leader. I'm not gonna try to control your minds or you know
It's just all you have to do is is though, you know, just live at the compound and you know
Be armed
I need some help Patrick ruin it. Yeah, well, it's okay
It's okay. Patrick donated and I think he's our other
donator. Pretty cool guys. That was unrelatable. Who donated? Someone donated the last
that was me
oh yeah oh hey thank you Dennis
the fuck that
I'm sorry I forgot
there you go yeah I forgot
thank you Dennis
he's not a bad person he's not a bad person
he's welcome in the chat too
I mean it's just off the panel
but yeah I mean he's kind of like
kind of came
in an interesting time
I know but yeah, I hope no one makes it personal. It's all you know, it's all it's all just fun
It's kind of entertaining to be here. I like the cat being able to
You know kind of direct the show in certain ways, but they want someone off the panel they can get someone off the panel pretty much
Yeah, doable
So I like your your are you always have this amazing artwork. So your art there looks like almost but almost I feel like it's a cube
I feel like the cube, you know, it's almost like with that pattern
I feel like almost a cube. That's what it looks like to me or kind of a gathering of
Magic gathering or something like that. No, and no, it's very it looks like a peacock feather a little bit
They're crucified at arms. I mean there's so much symbolism you can find in everything guys
That's why I kind of like trip out sometimes because it's like there's so many so many symbols and everything that it's like
What does it mean? What does it mean? Like when I was learning all of them. Wow, it was a process, but
Once I learned most of them, I just you know people have different name for different things. There's very universal symbols
there's basically, you know a few a few
major organizations
coming out with the
media. I mean, there's, there's it's very the next. We got easy. Easy. Yes, it's easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. It doesn't have to be difficult. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy makes things easy for me. I like it. He's my. Yeah, I know. I know. I came in with the other name and I'm like, let me stop doing that to him. He's getting confused. Yeah. I know. I am very easily confused. Sometimes, you know,
Then they'll get a little drunk and
People look different in their photos, but hey, everyone looks good tonight. You see I had asked my
I haven't even asked him. I hopefully don't okay. I'll play that good
Yeah, easy is very uh, he's a very attractive guy
He looks like Persian Ryan Gosling. Yeah. Oh my god. I love you. Thank you. Thank you
When you play cannon the Barbie move, but I really don't think Ryan Gosling he looks kind of like you know
He's bigger. Maybe like a guru or he
Maybe like a voodoo a voodoo a high priest or something. I don't know
Puerto Rico, right? You're Puerto Rican or Dominican. Okay, Puerto Rican. I love Puerto Rican guys
Puerto Rican I always noticed like the island guys are like a little bit more open-minded
Sexuality to know some of the Mexicans, but even Mexicans are kind of
We work when you work with Puerto Ricans in Mexicans and we joke about it
We joke about it. So we we we comfortable with that shit. We know we're not afraid of it
Yeah, I think it's like because they did some home Madonna whore complex with like a lot of the women in this country
I think it is like there's more experimenting that goes along with
I don't know it's like
People want to you know
You know it's a double standard. It's like women is like either Madonna or the whore, right?
There's no in-between in some some countries. I think America has a pretty good idea of a balance
Yeah. Everyone, everyone has
their four moments, right?
So, he's innocent. Yo, he's
fine. So, there's there's
everyone. Okay, that I pinned
the link. I can get pinned
the link. Oh, happy hump day.
Everybody is Wednesday. Oh, it's
7th of July. Second guys. It's
all it's hump day, people.
Yeah. Oh my god. Oh my god.
I uh, I kind of like I kind of like you know, I like talking to Chris K
I didn't like when it's sick was like trying to say like oh, yeah, he's gay
I'm sick. I'm not saying it would be like a dick about it. We're like, oh, he was
No, but Chris K was on last night and Chris K was actually serious and he's like, yeah
He's like he's down to do like a collab on chatter bait. He's down to like he's like, oh, he's like
Oh, he's got a big conversation was funny. I came along. Yeah. Yeah
So those it's interesting that he'd like
We can he used me to track the woman. I don't know who these who's these things we're gonna attract
usually
interesting
Kind of it's just different types of women are attracted. So I love you. He thinks that I don't know
Even if it was you know, stay a man in a wig. I'm gonna make this happen. Okay. We're gonna
Oh, okay. I'm just kidding.
Why don't you go look at my boy Sam?
He said, even if it's Sam back in the way, we don't want to die.
Also, back in a string trying to catch up. No easy does not look like that. He looks like guest on off
the Disney Cart
Merrill's creep a little bit
He's Puerto Rican Ryan Gosling. I got poor a Puerto Rican
I'm gonna give you the pictures. Yeah, cut us. Get ready. That's picture one is picture two
Okay, yeah, that one. Yeah, that's definitely Puerto Rican Ryan Gosling. Yeah, that's the important thing. I think I'm gonna say the Mario
Oh my god, okay, that's the one I drew the art of
He's having a little little sucky sucky on the what kind of drink it's long as he there's it here
Are you in your community service outfit there?
What is that?
Okay, you wear a bright reflective vest. Okay. Well, you look like a
Like a complete shirt. A shirt is a whole complete shirt. Oh, that's cool
I ain't helping them. What fuck is this texting and driving? You look you look just like I like exile because you have the same little
Patterns. Yeah, I'm gonna act out. You look like an old version of me. I
Gotta have this shake. I'm sick. I'm clearly fine
Jacob rendon now. I heard you were a demon
To me are there
Are there any truth to these rumors that you're a demon who's a demon who's who's calling who easy
Easy, I'm whatever. I'm whatever. I'm whatever you say. I am if I was it and why did you say?
I am in the paper the news every day. I am the fucker people call me
Right. I mean people that sounds like something a demon might say sir
the
Who was it this shit, but they're yeah, they're deceptive because they're trying to get they can communicate with humans
But they try to fool humans sometimes but they can also like like some humans and give them good information
But a lot of them don't like you
Tell us about this demonic stuff. It's a good one
Ask the chatter body says they want to be the ones talking about it. They know me so much at the chatter body
What is a good demon? In the King Solomon's, Goetia, the demons that they list there correspond to different...
That's a good approach, but that's not how you get an honest approach.
Different constellations, they're different constellations, they're different, maybe gods of different cultures that were...
Actually, gods in different cultures, they were demonized and put to the level of a demon because of the Bible.
Yeah, well the gen there's a similar story with the gen like and then also like you know Iblis
Didn't want to bow down to Adam and Eve and they have the old Lucifer didn't want to bow down to Adam
And they have the same kind of exact story where it's like the angels thought that they were superior to the man
and so
Because they were they were not made of the earth
Even though the earth is what brings us into physicality and so
You know, it's like we're kind of like better suited for Earth than they are in some ways, but you know
Think we're basically all trying to get out of here and get out of the hell's trying to try to rehab everybody
I think everybody has their
Their demons or their imperfections or problems, you know
I don't know, the more I've paid attention throughout life, I've realized that the spiritual and the physical are definitely connected and time has nothing to do with it. All of it is.
current even the best defense in a format in a dimensional setting or
Still running concurrent right now. Yeah, there's only the right and there's only the right now. There's you know, there's only
There's only right now. There's not the past or the future. Those are just the concepts
There's only the right now and time is all relative to the
spacing
You know have crystal Pepsi
I think that went out of
going out of
Circulation many many years ago. It was like a white color. That's right. It was clear
Yeah
Yeah, I don't know. I think I might have liked it. He's more kind of like seven up. So so
Is that redone to easy will smuggle a photo into his prison pocket so he can join panel
Oh, I'm telling you did look big
That's Doug D. Doug D's Barbara
Who was the chick that said you were a demon you remember I think it was I think he just has some
He's not a demon if he's a demon I mean he could be he was a member a member of the chat. Yeah
I
Oh, yeah, no, he is a demon. You'll see he's hateful. Well, it's okay
That's that's two trolls. There's all there's all my page on my dick. She think I want a fucking daughter. She's crazy
She's insane. There's there. There's no
Charisma's trying to take our second page
That's her, your charisma, that's you the whole time, Charisma, what did I ever do to you, Charisma, I'm a nice person, like, why are you picking on me?
Why don't you put the script on me?
Charisma, Hernandez.
Easy to be like, demons usually run in packs together.
Okay, well look, I don't want, I don't want, I don't want packs of demons necessarily in my panel, right? I'm trying to like, you know, you know...
What was that deal from the exorcist then?
The deal is that that was an extra system that has to do with more the Catholic Church in their belief, but extra systems, you know
There's certain ways of extra
If you were like, you know, you know, speak a lot
System on them evil people in your panel
What I would say I would say I you know, I would send all
On the chat, yeah, I said I sent all negative
negative energy
attention
evil eye
or any malice toward anybody on the panel or in the chat.
And I send that back to the sender,
a millionfold with love, okay?
And...
Barbara, we're ready to go through this, Barbara.
A millionfold, oh, God.
It was in the facts.
People are gonna end up in the grave.
Well, it's like but it's energy so it's like not really it's not gonna all
But there's no I also put love in there, too
And so the love like you know kind of like cancels it out
But you know just remember you're not supposed to be sending evil energy or like negativity toward people in a second
It affects other people
I
No, I said I got you that a million fall doesn't mean necessarily they go
No
No, all it is is that it's ending that sending the energy but it's any energy back
It doesn't what it won't actually multiply a million times, but you know
It'll do it'll do the trick to like make sure they know the energy was sent back
And that's you know, it's happened and my panel my chats will clear out after I say things like that because
Demons will flee like you know actual demons will flee. Let me see
They mad they mad that I'm not sad. They're not they mad that I'm not crying. We're being right
Okay, well
Bush's homo talking about enemy while never leaving their home amazing to me, okay all day every day, so what's your what's your deal so
How about a bunch of you talking about energy when they were leaving there? Oh, okay. So yeah, well, yes
There's energy. We're made of energy. We are no energetic beings. We're inside or outside
We're surrounded by energy. So I don't know what the problem is. Okay. Thank you. What's up money for 20?
We're gonna get past all this crap that's talked about us, right?
They guys are we isn't a great that we are definitely God I don't want to go
Don't know because he said trowel is trowel. Oh my gosh God
There's no energy a bunch of shit this happens go outside and make the most of it
There is no energy. Well, you don't know about you know, everything is energy base. I don't I don't know
I think I can't debate with somebody that's not making sense
Prisma easy watch out for a big bubba
Real racism
I know I know enough I know enough that I don't 66% of the time it works every time
66 oh gosh
well
66 very very evil number
Actually, what is like three divided by three point six six six you ever know that
You go everywhere the monster energy drink, right? Wait a minute. I'm really
Everything
Frequency of three six nine. How do you feel about yeah, that's that's the last Tesla, right?
Tesla has the three six nine stick the three six nine ratio, right?
Well, I don't know are you are we running on free energy yet? Obviously it hasn't been
You know pass on for the labor you know they pretty much ended the man installed all his work
But 85% of the world's technology runs on his technology
Well, they're the cars are named after him now
So he's probably smiling down from heaven looking at electric cars that are named after him and Elon Musk is benefiting from you know
He did some good
But yeah, you know everything's about money in this world. Unfortunately, we can't give away everything away for free because then you know
Who would like be you know, how is the paper? I don't know. Yeah, maybe it should be different. I don't know
I think it works. Okay. I'm KT. Hey KT money for 20 Jeff
Charisma, I don't know if there's nothing even you can just block easy and you want to see him in the chat
I mean, it's like and then I don't know what you follow him here. Like what's going on?
Thank you. Don't be blinded by the tempted. Oh my gosh
This attempted. I don't know. Oh my gosh
I'm sorry. I shouldn't read the comments out loud anymore. There's controversial
Yeah, I don't I don't want to like, you know
Yeah, the chat is all
Cat is their own entity. They say I can't really control with the chest
You can read it, but don't like get into it
But only if it's feel that the need to have somebody block them or you just take care of yourself
That's why I usually yeah, unless I'm talking to the chap. Where is the energy that? Oh
Okay, so when people say things like get a job, I think that's so offensive because you know, I've worked hard
I've never worked harder in my life than I worked. I I as for hours, you know, I I
Never even use six hours at a job. I can do like
Well, yeah, I mean it's fine, but it's like I'm working so people say that
And I'm not on any disability. I'm not on any SSI. I am not on any EBT or anything. And so it's like, you know
There's celebrities
me personally I get SSI because I'm retarded and gay
okay well that's fine if you're retarded and gay then I'm glad you have some because you're not you know
I don't know the streets to ask me for anything
well you can get a check for being gay
no you're definitely retarded though
I've been sleeping on this money
Guys guys
Page just pretend that you're transitioning to a man
Just pretend
We both can be gay and we can both get free money.
Think every time that he's the...
You know what, there's nothing that's free money.
Money is the energy and so however you get the money.
You got it from somewhere, so it's left from somewhere.
Why being gay was Paige?
I'm exactly gay because I'm straight.
Paige isn't straight and she's not...
You lost me.
Sike you lost me when you said energy is money is energy
It is
Money is a form of energy thinking about thinking about the energy and the things we can accomplish in the world with
The problem see psyche the problem is that you're not wrong
You're not wrong. You're just using the wrong word because when I hear the word when it's like you when I hear the word energy
I think about all of these
Individuals that are saying all the energy all the energy this energy that
So let's let's say more precisely, right? Let's use more precise words than the energy
Library please elaborate
You know, honestly, I'm pretty drunk. So I forgot even what I was talking about but I remember where I was
Don't know
We're talking about how your camera is off and a small
We're talking about how your camera is off
We're talking about how my homeboy right here right above or below or on the left
I don't know
We're talking about how my homeboy right here
My homeboy right here used to be on the short bus
And I remember because we were both there together
Oh shit, that
That we're on the short bus together. This nigga doesn't even know how to grind up his
Yeah, it's a currency currency and energy
How to grind up your weed, bro
There's a thing psyche. Let me put it like this
Time
Alley will current psyche time
Let's say instead of using the word energy
Let's use the word time. Let's use a unit of measurement
Hey guys, let's put hairs about you know, it's like the names that we get it's like energy time
It's a you know, it doesn't equal mc. Square. So energy goes math, you know
How are you afraid that have Edison and you know Thomas Edison made it energy
Yeah
Well, at least we can run, but you can't actually,
I bet you the log's gonna catch us fine.
Oh, it's, it's, it's current, why are you, it's current.
Hey, no, yeah, you're not supposed to talk about it.
No, no offense.
I don't know how to think offense to it,
it's just not, I don't know.
Cause I'm gay too, so I understand.
I know you're gay, I know you're gay,
you're a huge flamer, is that you and me,
you're too gay for me.
You're like too much, you're too much,
you're too much of a bottom for me to deal with.
I don't really have sex with men.
That means you're gay.
Okay.
Yeah, no, but I'm not gay. Say we're good. You're becoming trans
No, no, you want to keep your keep your meat. Okay. Well, you know, you always wear a dress
Yeah
Thank you
Everyday
I don't I don't like I don't like I don't like
Whatever it is, I don't care if it's a chick I don't care
But this guy right here. This guy right here. What is the brand of the blunt?
I'm not asking you I'm asking the guy. I don't know. I'm asking you talking to
I smoke weed I smoke weed
the blunt rap
The blunt rap is none of
called many a brand
was it a game, was it a backwood, was it, like, what the fuck was it, it looked like, was it a Phillies, was it nuts?
You look like
He's really the entire show okay say no stop. No, I can't take it anymore. I'm not gonna hear talk about
What brand the blunt rap is like it's
Everyone started yelling and it's like
The most the least important question he just wants to argue and start profit
This is it's either growing on about
He admitted it yourself a self-amended retard not even high-function autism
And then what if you wanted to you know, he wants to be gay. I don't want I don't want it to be gay
I don't know, I don't know that you didn't stick, and please...
No, no, he's always been gay since I made him, that's for sure.
He has.
I don't know.
Stay tuned, get your bitch ass up here!
You see Saki, you can fix it, right?
Stay tuned!
I mean gay in a whole other way though, I mean like weird gay.
You're gay?
No, I mean he's weird gay.
Oh yeah, oh he's weird gay, yeah.
Well, you know, it's like, I mean, I don't even know, I don't even know if it's gay, it's just like, he's like, he's like, I don't think he's ever, I don't think he's ever stuck to, I think he's probably only stuck to one or two dicks, but he did tell 400 glow or 100 glow that he was going to come meet up with them and have sex with them.
And then he was being very serious about it, I don't know, he might be just trolling, I'm not sure.
I think I think he's a whack troll to be honest with you, but I mean yeah, I think you're definitely some
Developmental if you if he actually goes if you go through with it. It's a good show
That yeah
Yeah, I mean there's just good trolls or bad trolls. I don't come here to troll. I actually get entertainment out of this channel
Functions, okay, I mean trolls. I mean
Really chose to entertain you. I don't care
I brought shows here intentionally and I knew there was gonna be so I was wanting for very high high ratio
full chats and stuff. I know I didn't think it was even as bad as it is, but
You know, it's kind of better than I thought it would be too easy. Okay, so I'm sorry. I don't need to read comments
Psychi is yeah, I'm not impeding six energies
They was sucking my energy like a vampire off my off the town
You know, I'm like my eyes are like about to close if he's droning on and on about blunt wraps. I mean what a topic
I mean, he's obviously not that much of a weed connoisseur because he would have been able to tell that it's a Dutch.
Now, what kind of Dutch? I don't know.
They only sell backwards only now. They only sell backwards now.
California Archie.
Yeah, Swisher's Suites and Black & Mouth are gone.
Yeah, they did away with a lot of the flavor stuff, so it doesn't quote unquote entice children.
You're right
Ridiculous, you'll be gorgeing. Oh, oh, come on guys stop making me read it bad comments. Let's stop it
No, I'm just trying to like
Interact with the chat and everything I can't read. I don't know. I haven't read a chat and 81 comments it says
Oh my gosh. Well, I mean the chat I do like you know the chat is active. There's dirt 36 people here
I don't know. Oh my gosh, guys. See, I'll be I'll be I'll be polite. Um, yeah, smile. I like this one. There's a smile in the chat. I like the smile.
Let's just all have a smile, a laugh. Let's have that be awesome. Like he was doing a terry. You know what this room needs.
What? Smile. I did not. Someone said I caught. Who want to come with me?
So okay, so I said Seiki was doing a tear reading and called beta it old maid, but he just
pulled the wrong deck. No, I did not call it say that
Batman what were you laughing about or Barbara laughing? I mean, she has great big hat
Okay, I'm gonna stop reading the call. I'm not gonna look but you said you were gonna stop like four times ago
But they're they're going they're going so fat. Oh, what's it? What is it? Say that on? Oh, yeah
Okay, oh my god, are you there it looks like you're falling guys. Oh, here are you?
Good point we can't disappoint
Crack under my chair. Oh my god
Definitely smoke crack
Underneath your chair
That's where the best crack is page. Don't you know what?
Underneath the chair is where the best crack is
Well, I'm gonna get signed. I'm gonna get signed. You heard you heard
G listen
Allegedly I might be going live in jail. Don't worry about it
You know, you know, you know the a1 order with the afro
Afro glasses a1 order
Oh, you don't want a order though. He got a pro. He got glasses. He went live in jail like two months back
I
So you're gonna do
Know that's who you was I saw okay easy. Okay, so he's okay. Okay, I don't like it down the chest
Allegedly, we will throw it on there. Yeah, be nice to the chat every day to the panel chef
Well, yeah, I mean everything's like, you know, there's like
Everyone wants to jump on the the witch the witch trials right and that's someone that has you know
Executed witches in my in my ancestry, you know, I'm a little bit
I drew that evil guy that came from there.
Oh, I don't judge easy, I got homeboys doing life in person.
You too, I got homeboys doing life.
That's fine, they usually have their life.
A lot of times they're happy in there, they have plenty of gay sex and free meals
and a free place to live forever.
I mean, it's not a bad deal for a life.
I mean, it's not necessarily good.
I think guys in there are bad.
You know what I'm saying? It's nothing to me.
And my booty didn't get touched, so it's nothing to me, yeah?
Well, if I had life in prison, my booty would be open for business.
Wait, what's up?
What's up?
My booty
The serpent jelly packets I get the jelly I get the jelly
What you people in chat if y'all just trying to cancel easy and shit
Is not going to offend me unless he's harmed a child or a right
I don't, I don't, I don't want to, I don't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he doesn't, he
Thank you
We can't ask that become somebody
Because yeah, because somebody keeps calling you away. I know it's like, you know, it's not very nice
I mean, it's like I don't think there's anything wrong being called a wiss or whatever
But it's just a arbitrary term and like a lot of ways it's pinched. He pinched a woman right in her
Hey
They think they're gonna repeat it over and over. Y'all look so stupid. They already know
Know all of it. Y'all look so dumb keep on trying your hardest to bring me down. Well, I'm still so happy
He was like saying you know, he was like, you know, he was he was he was he was saying I was on his naughty list and like
Like he was smitten
Well, Santa Claus Santa come back. We love you and he was like I won I won I won
Well
Like I've never seen someone's grandpa act such ways play super games when super prizes and so, you know
Some people just were playing super games
No, it's a really good thing it comes out of it, you know, we can laugh sometimes that yeah
Exactly because me and Dennis and was thinking alike. I was just gonna let him celebrate a little bit longer
If you guys were up like on like if I could see your guys's eyes like I just looked at all your little
scratch you just see you guys staring back at me we're all looking at each other like what the
fuck is going on right now yeah yeah tell me life tell me sweet little life I'm simply funny
screenshots of you making faces they can't honestly they can't even focus on the conversation we
I was expecting somebody to come get the grandfather or someone to take your old ass to bed, but that didn't happen. So I figured he was just a lonely old man.
Well, we can't be telling people to go to bed when we're not going to come from the place.
He's got the company of the kids. He didn't even have no case. Casey was like Casey was like, oh, you know
He was
Okay, okay, Paige you have this
Make yourself big yeah
Okay, okay, so this is like the six of the six of the six of cups, you know, of course is like the nostalgia cars like
memories of some kind of happiness or
You know having nostalgia about happy times, but also, you know bringing these traditions to your own family to your own
No, your own kids and your family and this through
Remember in the innocence and how simple the world used to be, right?
You've been feeling that lately and also feeling like you've been kind of like left out of this new world
maybe or something or like this new world is like
go in so fast and
You're like if I blink you might miss it, you know, but you're still you're still
No, you're still really in it. It's like the world has has changed, but you know, and it is a little bit colder, but
Okay, we've got the tower card. I think there's like, you know, this is like the I know we all dread these towers and there's
But they are they they are these are great
clears of energy and a great way to
Open your life up for for new energies. Okay?
You got that tower and maybe like also because they were like feeling left outside here and then like the tower came up
It's almost like maybe it's a good thing. You know, you don't go in the tower
Maybe this is a warning to like stay out of this tower or something there could be some kind of like, you know
Don't know. I just got that feeling seeing those two cards together because it kind of reminds me that the window kind of looks like
It could be part of that tower, right? Okay
Your advice for this is you know, it's a it's a game to like a game feel like a competition. She's like have fun
I
Don't know. This is fairly
what it's kind of referring to, but it's like, you know,
it's like, just expect there's gonna be chaos
and just kind of ride with it.
And you're I think you're doing really well for one more part
I don't like to do that. Oh, yeah, and it's like yeah, you got the hangman reverse
You're gonna come out of feeling trapped or you're gonna come out of you're gonna come out of this feeling like you can't make a move
Or you're like or you're not making the movie one it you're coming out of that
It's the hangman reverse. You're also got the enlightenment with that. So hold on. Let me see. Oh, oh, yeah
Okay, so that was good. Thank you
You're welcome
My pleasure
How's everyone tattooing doing? How's everyone doing? Yeah, so yeah guys we want to be we want to be like no
Cognizant I'm like people nice
Yeah, we don't know you don't we want to forgive up. We don't have these a set of forgiveness
I would think I'm not trying to put words words in anybody's mind or about I'm saying like it is better to
Forgive because it's like basically it's almost like forgiving yourself first, right?
Thank you cells has asked. How do you think he has a California bench?
All right, if I don't know the money I make on chatterbait I could I don't like I could buy a bagel a month
I mean, it's like I'm not
No, I think my YouTube is a little bit more lucrative than my my my adult material. So
Yeah, Chris K because I needed I needed the the collaboration with Chris K a little spice I'll spice up the channel a little bit
He said he's willing to he said he said he knows we're sending there are they're sending some some tokens and stuff
Seiki all day every day is easy. I'd love easy Barbara
Yep, we got Barbara in the chat. Why you start talking negatives all on you. Yeah, well, I'm not talking my talking negative
I don't know good job Barbara. It's like he has okay, so let me see
All day every day. Let's see. Don't worry. Don't worry. Yeah
Guys that's also like that's a remedy prayer. Lord. Give me the strength that you know, give me the wisdom to know
It's a surrender to what I cannot change the wisdom to know
Or the you know the ability to change what I can change and the wisdom to know the difference, right?
Something like that. I didn't say it perfectly, but
You know, oh look at we were dropping like people dropping like flies on the panel, you know
It's because I got to keep you only the heavy hitters left
You're part of the part of the group now. I forgot who just drops guys. I'm gonna strike. I don't know. They weren't talking
Yep. Hey Barbara. Are you here Jenna's in or no?
Yes
Okay, here
Yep, so
We're about so you I don't know if you want to share you want to give the exact state you can say this
America if you want you
You're from Merica. Okay, Merica, so maybe
That sounds like some of the people from the south or northeast would say okay all day every day your new England liar
Hey tea. Oh
All day every day is from the girls in the shower. Okay. I thought yours
Sometimes I think people are saying that. Oh
their name yeah, so do you have a wife or are you are you know?
No, you can't read you. Are you just it in me? Oh
Like I'm waiting for a guy. Are you the guy I've been waiting for
No, we went over this I'm too
repressed
I was hoping I always hope the answer will be different if I keep asking
Yeah, okay. Yeah every day all day. Well, I mean, I'm already practically engaged to Chris K now and that's actually just one
No, you're not second best, but you have to like, you know, you can you can stand you can stand out your Chris
I think I'm a lot better looking than Chris. Just be honest. Well, I
All I can see is like, I just see this picture of like, I see a beautiful blue light, you know
I don't know what you're looking at. Have you come toward the light, Carol Ann?
Okay. No, it's don't go toward the light. The light takes you to the other world.
That's what he wanted. He wanted you to draw a picture of me so he could make fun of me, but you did a great...
Okay, yeah, I'm sorry, Barbara. I tried to, yeah, I mean, I hope it wasn't to make fun of you. Who did that?
Yzzy did that?
Yzzy.
Barbara is okay, so I think I'm just getting help sticky for her robe. Oh
My gosh, oh
Okay, see the left okay
Yeah, Barbara's not a rogue mob barbers a great mod and you know, it's like I I didn't remod a few people
There are really people I'm gonna stick in you guys, you know, I really don't want to mod everybody and basically, you know
If I think you'd be a good mod, I'll probably I'll probably let you know
You can let me know if like, you know, you think it was unfair that I grew up on some people
I maybe was but I just had to start from I love starting from scratch and then like you know being able to like clear out and you know sometimes
You know the do-over is not perfect either, but you know
Long as we keep keep trying do over Barbara is the best. Yeah, Barbara's pretty awesome. Do you have you know how to spell?
Psyche Barbara. I'm sure she does. Tsy, CH, B.
What time is it? Oh, it's 4.40. I still have this beer left.
I'm drinking very slow today, obviously. I don't know if I'll...
Are we doing good, guys? I'm kind of quiet.
I'm thinking about cheesesteak. Oh, okay. Okay. Oh, here's a cheesesteak. I love a good filly cheesesteak
Hey, G. Hey, G. Cool. Yeah
Like I don't know what just happened. My stream yard's being super weird
Yeah
It's been asking me to log in and stuff and usually it's always been logged in already so I don't know about that.
Look at how bruised my elbow is from hitting it on the fucking chair.
Oh my gosh. How did you do that?
That's good. Why am I bruising like a little peach? What's going on? Maybe I have low iron probably.
Oh, yeah, you're using like an old lady
Yeah, that's bad looks dirty, but it's just bruised shit. Oh my gosh. Well, you know, I'm from my heart. We're good
Yeah, I mean, I mean some bruises look worse. They do you hear it really hard on something? How'd you injure your arm? I?
Just waxed it on the fucking chair bunch tonight
Yeah, and like probably
Okay, you're not the lightning page who who hit you page up. I live alone. No, we know we hit me
I'll fuck a mother fuck her up if I see
The elbow anyway
Never the true story never see a black corresponding bruises on your knees, you know, I dare this oh my god. It's a mystery
Dance no, I'm so really bad ones on my leg just from just being like, I don't know clumsy
Did you get varicose veins? Have you heard of this? Yeah, I don't have them yet. I'm not that I'm not
Well, I mean we get right you need a pregnant people sometimes people get them and they get pregnant
They cause the camera is the brings you can cause hemorrhoids and varicose veins pop out
I don't if they are very common. Where's as in air McLeer? I don't know. I was here earlier and I hate summer
Summer yeah, and also, um, so gaudy and
Who is the other gentleman his Patrick something, you know, we'll see you tomorrow night guy. It's not a gentleman. He's not a gentleman
Yeah, but he was you know, you know
Yeah
The internet drama
Yeah, she's mystery. Oh, yeah, have you see? Oh, yeah, Alex. Yeah, I heard I heard Alex. There's something bad
But it's like I kind of call it the Streisand effect with the Streisand effect was Barbara Streisand had a house in Malibu
Right and so then they came out with a Google imaging above their house, right?
So it was basically the whole floor plan of the house is that basically on the internet, right?
This is when it just came out to Google the Google
Imaging right came out so she like filed a lawsuit and like made a big deal about it
it's like to get it taken off and
Like before like she filed a lawsuit there was like ten views on the pro honor property
Like after she filed a lawsuit there are like a hundred thousand
So it's like when you sometimes you can bring attention to something and it's like but it's called a stri-sand effect
It's like when you bring something and it makes the situation worse because you brought attention to it
so I kind of like
You know avoid
People know same people say like sometimes was docking stuff I try to like
Yeah, I don't want to keep bringing it up it bring more attention. It was like he was here earlier. No man. No one can turn it
I kept him off because he was yelling too loud. He was screaming and
being very offensive to
Some of the people in the panel as usual. Yeah, it was Hollywood. They're a bunch. Oh my god. Oh, I don't look all fresh every
That's like it too much in the politics. I don't know what goes on
Playboy mansion parties. I've never been invited. Okay, I'm very barely invited to my own freak offs. I'm barely invited to okay
So I'm very very alone. Okay. I haven't heard from a few days. That's why yeah
He's been here's here last night page behind enemy lines deep undercover for beta. Oh, well
Okay, you know, be the undercover for beta. Yeah, I don't think I think Paige is a very like, you know, maybe she maybe she's a little bit
All people can be biased in relationships. I think she's as neutral as you can get when it comes to like the drama
She's working for true. No
Oh, no, that's what the fucker for sure. No, my gosh guys, please
You know, I want people that work for themselves not for some
I work for me
um
Independent contractor divine I guess so let's go with let's go with let's go with and my boss
Yeah, we're butch. I work for her too
This is spandela. No, that was my boss. Oh
I said work for my boss and I work for the divine. I guess. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I like that
I think I'm like, you know working for the the hired the hired good, you know, I like to be J
Like the you know burger king be care of the British nights this one burger king for sure
Burger King or British nights. I'm not sure. I don't see this flame broiled man
Flame Royals. Yeah, that's where it is. Go from
Flames well in people still said flame flames that flamers are bad, you know make burgers taste delicious
Okay, you know me mark. I like my bear cold my TV loud and my homosexuals for naming
Well, hopefully you don't mean it literally on fire
No
Yeah, it's both, you know flaming from the Simpsons. It means it I yes, but the flame
The joke didn't age well because it made me breathe some mind like
Gaze being put on the on the stakes and burnt like the wishes which happened to around that time, you know
But flaming
Double on time, but there's like a lot of stuff like you know even the word f-a-g-g-o-t is you know
That actually is a bundle it can almost be you almost like a piece of sage
It kind of looks like this kind of like the fat like the Roman fasties, but it's like, you know
It can be called the F-A-G-G-O-T, and they're said to take these little bundles of sticks
and throw them into the fire to make them catch on fire when they're burning people.
So there's a lot of history, especially with the fire.
You know, I don't know there's I think it's part of the Psyop too also the gay flag is interesting because it has you know
The rainbow the rainbow, but the it's the uh, it's basically all the colors the shocker system upside down
I don't know what the subliminal
Meaning of having the shocker system upside down on the flat. I don't know. It's just like I don't think that's I don't know
If that was the pattern of the normal rainbow or whatever, but it is an upside down shocker
So we're starting with the red on the top instead of the purple, right?
Um, yeah, you just block you can someone in chat bothers you guys you can just block them
You know just put their name and say block you won't see them anymore
You might see them on the screen if I have the chat up there, but
It's a burger eyes
How are you doing Mikey? Have you the to read my comments? Okay? Yeah, let's not fight. We guys it's been fighting for hours
I mean, it's they literally been
You know hours of fighting I
Want to share love
He's just like he reminds me of like everything the uh, I'm kind of sexy librarian like she's like she's like
She's like he's very stern as a sh but she's like
She runs that library because he is not that important. Oh, he's not important to
page or she's my I don't know my jokes was gonna joke. I mean
What was the mother of shepherd's story being complete BS of the mother?
Matthew Shepard. And Matthew Shepard does probably sigh. I mean a lot of stuff is probably sigh. I'll be honest
That was a time, you know, there was like a lot of
Political stuff going on with the gays and then it brought a lot of sympathy
Weird even I just don't know it made it seem like you know
Great people are praying, trying to like beat up gay people. I know it's happened, but it's I think it's very very rare
But that is sad if it didn't happen, but his name is Matthew Shepard. He was hanging up the scarecrow
There's certain details that I recognize as classic psychological operation
Hells but I can't get too much things on the show
Summer if you're still here like maybe I'll talk to you later today, but I've got a few things that
Channels for you. It was really random, but it's must be big stuff. So just
I'll talk to you about it later
Glitterly glitterly glitterly holy fuck page moment. Okay glittery gel pen to blue gel pen. It's very cute like summer
Oops, I did it again. I just britneyed my elbow
I'm Britney. I'm constantly britneying myself. I all I need to do is shave my head
You know take a
2007-2009 Brit when she had no fucking hair mental breakdown poor thing. Yeah
Hopefully I hope I don't get there. I see you. I see you keep my umbrella handy
Case I need to take the window out of an SUV. Az, what planet were you on 20 minutes ago?
What planet? Wow. Easy as an alien. It's KT. Bye-bye.
Okay, I don't know what's going on.
This chat is taking on a life in the zone. It's become a Frankenstein. Honestly, it is like, no.
My chat it's been the chat of my room. I think it's like Frankenstein has become unrecognizable to me
you know, I still see some of the features of the
Cat that was but you know, it's like now there's you know, it looks all different and
He's somebody that I used to know somebody
No, I mean it's like he's
Frankenstein, but gosh guys what when I created this show I took all these like
Ideas and some of them were like ideas that were not really in use anymore. I
Brought them back to life in this
My show is like a Frankenstein. I don't know. It's like kind of like kind of like that looks like how like that
Like a saying
But it's like if it it's like it's kind of gaining it has the possibility of gaining self-aware, but I kind of
It's kind of gotten bigger than me. So
You know, I'm just I'm just here for the ride to you guys, right cat has oh I use oh no
I'm not denying the chat energy. It's gosh. I'm the same. I have energy too. Okay, everyone's energy is important page
Whenever you could can I either reading even if it's not today? Yeah summer. She has a message for you if you want to come up
You have some time
They she's been writing stuff down
Yeah
Well, did you hear what I said some or like or is or you just like did she might have been away at the time
She might have been away at the time like did you hear it or you in the chat?
Or did you just come around and we back and be like hey could you or what?
Anyway, and yes, you can have a reading anytime you like you just ask my girl. I'm here for you always
Yeah, here you go. There we see
Summer. What's up girl? What's up everybody? How are you? I'm tired. Retired?
I'll put the page back on. Alright, just woke up a little bit ago.
Well then I don't want to come at you. You just open your eyes. No, you're good.
Okay, so I had been listening just just I call it a niggle. I don't know just chatter
But so like a big event is coming soon or like or it's like just something's causing you like anxiety and anticipation
And it's exciting, but it's also scary
and like thinking of maybe making like a
physical appearance change, I don't know if it's hair color or length or another
tattoo or a piercene or just something nails just it's something just like
that that's something something little but big in a way it's going to fulfill
something for you that you need right now because I think you're going through a
little bit stuff. I think that you've had like a weird this is so crazy so
I was shown like, okay, so you've been kind of like spooked by your own shadow, but it's not your own shadow
And it's not just because you're like emotionally wound right now
It's because you actually had like a paranormal activity experience like something it's it's not anything bad
It was just it caught you off guard and you had to question or think about it
Or you saw something or you had like a time glitch experience or like a loop or just something of long that like esoteric kind of
paranormal
experience and it kind of has like been on your mind a little bit and
I'm not sure how you feel about those things or if you're used to it or not
But I do think that it was like it you almost thought you jumped from your own shadow like you were standing behind yourself, which is weird
Also, I do feel like there's something about your husband's like job or help like you're waiting on news or that you're
expecting to get news about
maybe health or a job, but it's like
It's not a bad. It's positive. It's going to be positive news
So like I don't know if it's going to be like a raise or a position change or just like I just a general change for him
That's necessary. That's when it comes to when they say health like I took you don't have to take it in a physical sense
It's like mental health or his emotional health like there's something that's going to change that
Necessary right now
Anyways
And something about moving your furniture or cleansing or just like you're trying to shift something in your house
You're trying to shift the energy for some reason. Anyways, those that was just what I channeled like that's just what I was
Heard your name when he popped in and I was like I just need to write that down
Thank you beautiful
Yeah, I mean we can I think we'd be like a little bit of positive clarity here for some of those things
Those were just the things that were like
They obviously were pulsating, you know, they needed to be they need to be
You need to know that someone acknowledges what you're going through because you help everybody and a lot of the time
No one's there for you
And that you're loved and so is your husband and that
you guys
You're such good people that no matter what happens in this world. You're always going to be
There's always going to be a gold shiny chair
You know what I mean for both of you and most best places of when we leave the service like
You're just you're you're one of the most amazing people and you're very selfless and there's just
Nothing that's not special about you
Okay, the night of Raphael. So romantic, dramatic, poetic, introspective, um, so committed romantic relationships being swept off your feet, situations or topics that make your heart flutter. I like that card. Um, it kind of does clarify like maybe...
Maybe you guys just need that you know to take a break from some things like you need to go away together
You need to just kind of reconnect and I feel like there's a lot of people going through this right now because it's not the first
It's coming out differently
But there's a lot of people in our community that are going through this where they need to re spark or start dating again
Just do something that's like fun and playful together. That's spontaneous and different you shouldn't have to plan to
date your partner in a sense and that you know what I mean not that I'm saying that you are I'm just saying just
Yeah, we're going on a date Saturday. Yeah, okay, there we go. Thank you. Thank you
And yeah, you should still be especially when you've been together for 17 years
You have to you have to right? It's up to us to keep that fire going, right? It is all right
No, you can't can't have a fire without any wood and if there's nobody getting the wood then there's not going to be a fire
Hopefully I'm getting some wood. No, I'm just gonna get some wood. You're gonna get some wood. Look at him brush and then give it to you
Hello
I thought that'd be funny
All right, I would like one more for her, please
Holy fuck. Oh, thank you
Oh my gosh, I'm so short. Okay, and the tallest chair is ever like my feet angle like this
Okay
Prosperity rising from wise planning time to take the next step optimistic plans that turn out as expected
So it's like waiting for your ships to come in and then they do
With great positivity and great news like a white dove kind of news
So that kind of correlates with the waiting on maybe some news like I wrote down
Right, just one more and then I'll let you go
Okay, okay
I'm definitely waiting on some names.
Okay, well it's coming. It's coming. Look at you standing there waiting, but you're not waiting
Because your backs turn to the ship. So that means that you've already like the news is coming to you
It's going to arrive right you're not looking on the horizon waiting for the ships
Okay, so we have three that came out and I'm going to take them for you
So we have the four of Rafael so seek out other possibilities look for the magic in life and be aware of your own emotions
the aid of Gabriel. A great deal of activity, sudden and immediate results, and important
communication. There we go. Look at that with all her birds and owls. And then we have the
page of Arielle. So reliable, clever, educated, and balanced. That's very much you.
So an excellent opportunity will be offered to you. Scholarships or the pursuit of education, time to get to work.
Summer, whatcha doing girl? Planning something always eh?
Yeah, there's always stuff going on.
Signs.
All right, so you watch for the signs you notice and you trust the signs that heaven continually sends you and you do like
I know that you're very open to the number
Synchronicities and like a song that might connect to something, you know, you're very open to that
You see like a bird. Yeah, like oh, you know
I wonder what that bird means because I felt like maybe I need to do more research on that because it just had I had a
Moment with it, right? It was very present. Yeah
So, oh, look at that joy is flipped with that and I didn't even realize beautiful
so
By enjoying this moment. I'm giving thanks to God for my life
You know, you are very connected to like you have jobs down here, too
We're all employees of the up. We know that right so right you do that all the time and you do you bring so much joy to people's lives
You can take a tragedy and you can make it
You can make it a fucking a secret garden. You know what I mean? You could just take anything and make it beautiful
Oh summer you're such a fucking beautiful soul
And we don't plan a date for sex, by the way, we have sex all the time in the chat.
No, I was reading somebody's like, plan a date for sex.
I'm like, no, no, no.
Going out on a date, you should date people, not to you Paige, not to you, not to you.
People should date. It's okay
Yeah, I was like an example of where like, you know, our
Relationships after so many years can go a little bit
Stagnant because we get comfortable and we forget to treat our partner as as our girlfriend or boyfriend
So like you still have to keep dating and always pursue them
Yeah, so action came flying out
And you're our action taker, always. You're the world's action taker. There's nothing that you can't handle.
So today I take action related to the priorities that I have previously put off.
So are you probably... I would say...
tying up loose ends in some way or just like doing little odd jobs that you've left on unfinished around maybe the house or
Just little odd things that you're like you're just trying to bring everything together and consolidate it in a sense, right?
So it's not everywhere because I think you're more like OCD summer. I think you like that.
I can't be.
With certain things like if there's particulars there's different um, there's this spectrum and the OCD
Don't know what you call it like that. I don't want to call it a disease or like I don't know
It's that thing when you when you're OCD, right? There's different like levels of it, right different categories
Okay, if I can I'm gonna do maybe one spell card for you somewhere actually because we keep talking about spells tonight
And I've had the duck sitting here shuffled for like ever
Oh, I
No, you make me work for it girl
Okay, ooh
So the wheel of the year, this is wonderful. These are really cool cards actually
So it says as the season changed so do we and actually we could all probably resonate with this one
I'm just gonna say that right now. That's what I'm being told so everyone will listen
Which is follow the wisdom of nature to inform their magic rituals as a way to live with purpose the eight
sabbats holy days
Celebrate the particular lessons and magical opportunities that occur within each season
These days are Samhain, Yule, and I'm Balak, Astra, Batain, Midsummer. Oh, I don't know this one with the L
Lagnasa and Mabam
as of now
Where we are in the wheel. What does this time of year signify for you?
And what obstacles or opportunities are emerging look deeper into the meaning of whatever season
We are in to help guide and navigate your magical rights
Interesting
I've never thought before so basically it's just you know
We need to think about where we are where we've come from and why and how it how it affected us and
Use that to
Kind of create our own what is it wheel of fortune, you know what I mean because we don't we don't want we know
So let's fill it with the things that we do want, release the things that we don't, move forward with that knowledge and that lesson learned so that Karma doesn't follow us and we don't have to repeat it.
And then we have like all of our nice little things on this wheel, right? And we get to choose, but we have the choice to go either way with it always, guys.
Anyway, here you go. I love you Summer, thank you.
Thank you, beautiful love you too.
You're welcome, I hope that you guys have a great day, you and your husband.
Let me get work. I'm chillin. I got outreach tonight. Oh
To do this for you guys and I love doing that for you
Appreciate your talent golly. Oh, thanks
It's not much of a talent. I'm just a weirdo while you're getting actually not really
and if you are it's okay because we're all weirdos so in a way well I think
that's why we all hang right because your vibe attracts your tribe well money
you thought today was Tuesday your time glitch you know I wrote that down
listen to matrix guys listen to me
yeah well yeah it's Wednesday
It was only Wednesday. Oh my gosh. Yeah, there's only he's only half gone. Nicole. Who's James?
James
Oh, there's okay, there's Nicole Hayes games and then there's games love
Yeah, and guys we have hold in my cock is in the room
It's really fun to say what a neat
Yeah
Yeah, I mean, I've heard of the macaque's family, but you know, it's just kind of a little
It's funny how the name turned out holding holding macaque, okay until I meet our summer stay I only got outreach
I know I say I got ours and then I realized it was a Wednesday. Oh, yeah. Yeah, you know, it's Wednesday when summers
It's really in the streets
Street's helping people so it says many Mikey is my probe pretty no filters
Mikey yeah, you know
My filters don't really improve my list. I mean I
Don't really use a filter on my show
Sometimes I can't if I'm on YouTube live, but let's resume your
Money you have the last day all day. He lost a whole day
Yeah, I've done that too guys. I mean the other day I named my stream the other day. I was like happy Sunday
Or though someone was like, oh my god, like it's Saturday night. I'm like, oh my god
I was hoping it was closer to the weekend, but oh well
My day that I'm like, oh, okay, cuz I know it's outreach day. So like other than that everything just kind of blends together
That's fair. Yeah
Well, I think I'm not gonna start and then I might have to put a bed soon
I have to have an idea. It's not like that. I said the knaps between my shifts in my life
All right
Yeah, well, I have to work, but that's not telling me late. I
Came up with Christ last night. Well, I have to rip and
Slight I went to sleep
I've been crying a lot lately.
It's a great unbecoming of me.
Oh, something happens.
Sometimes you got to clear yourself.
That's true.
I think like tears, I have heard like tears.
Like there's like a lot of magnesium in tears
and it might be like a natural way to like...
Uh, clear up magnesium. I don't know. There's drink our tears if we'll stay young. Maybe that's the secret
I would not do that. That's a little bit more
But I would say you can uh
They've looked at the under microscope a sad tear and a happy tear different
Look to them. They have a different chemical makeup. There's some kind of difference. So there's different tears
We have different kind of tears for them. I'm gonna come take your tears psyche. Oh
Yeah, come collect them and see a little bottle and you can live forever. I'm just kidding. No, they're not that powerful, but
My tears my tears will probably
Turn people to dock eat. I'm not sure. I don't know. I mean the golden ass
For mail involved this oh
Yeah, people will need it. Just rub your tears on the foot on the head on the scale. No
okay no it's we're just kidding welcome welcome back I just remember I just
think about when Alice the Wonderland you know she likes she got all big and
then she like started crying and then she got to turn small again and like the
tears and it's like four good whole ocean who could vowel caterpillar yells at
No, it's a you know, it's actually like it was a little it was a little little cake and a little red
Yeah, the piece of bread and I was the is the potion and so
And a mushroom but the ones that mother give you don't do anything at all. Yeah
Yeah, well the one the caterpillar gave works at her direction almost eyes and then that eat me and drink me
Grew her and shrunk her
She also if she got big again at the rabbit's house remember she like ate the
She took some of the cakes with her. She ate some of her abs.
Yeah, she was like, she wore the house like an outfit.
The outfit was pretty crazy. Yeah, pretty great.
I love that.
Bill at Lizard. I used to watch it. Well, there wasn't a really good
Alice of Wonderland movie made in the 80s. It had like Carol Channing as like the
Red Queen or the White Queen. And about the 80s, I think it might be still on
available on YouTube or something. It's a really great Alice of Wonderland. Look at the 80s one with Carol Channing and
I think it has a Ben Ben
Ben
Black guy Ben Ruin or this black guy that was in luck a lot of a
You remember Zubli's do you played like kind of lying on Zubli's
It was a PBS public access. I feel like that's black. I remember
You're up too.
It's a long time to have a good show, right?
They're like these animals.
Yeah, they're like these animals.
They're human and just an animal.
They're like a parrot.
The woman just is a parrot.
Yeah, I remember.
Oh, okay.
I know what you're talking about.
Ew, I didn't like them.
It's fucking weird.
Yeah, I didn't like them.
Yeah, it was, it was weird to me too. I was like, this is fucking weird.
Yeah, look at the furries, look at the furries show for the 80s.
Yeah, that was the new stage of the furries back then.
The bronies were just the idea in some people's heads at that time.
And now look at the bronies there. They're just absolutely serial killers.
Yeah, oh yeah. The bronies are very weird.
men men that are into my other really any gronies left
I think most of them got taken out
But no, but I think there are I mean if there are bronies and it's like, you know, but yeah, like a lot of them
There's like the my little pony
K. L. E. R. This guy he like he set up a FedEx building and then himself
Of course because he wanted to be in the afterlife with Applejack or something. I don't know
It's one of the my little poses. I love what the cereal
No
Shetland pony at my grandparents farm, and it's fucking your name is Apple Jacks, and she's a jerk
Yeah, you can't name your animal or
He hates the kids like their only purpose and she hates the kids and so no one goes
She just eats and she just hates kids
The cockatoo lady. Oh, yeah, I love cockatoo. Well, you know, not everybody's a kid person or animal
I guess
Yeah, she's like fuck these kids get him off me now. I'm gonna bite them
I mean, I can't say I blame her. They're on her back all day and I'm kicking her and shit pull her hair like
I feel about kids. I
Mean, I have a lot of kids, but you know
This kind of found upon the view by random kids
Well, yeah
City prosecutors don't like that
Her neck is too short
She can't bite them she just tries cuz you're next to short
Just politely stick your foot out and just kindly trip them don't bite them
I like to take candy and shake it in my hand and then I throw it out into the middle of the street and see what happens
It's a good. It's a good.
60 to zero real quick.
60 to zero.
It's a little like a little
infanticide between friends,
you know, to spice it up a little,
you know?
Yeah, no, it's funny.
It's funny.
Can I put candy in my head
and check it up and see
when you run out to the street?
What happens?
Yeah.
I don't think you'd taste candy. I think you might taste we put it like a handful of titties
We just toss titties in the street. You'll go there. There you go. We've heard some titties
for that again
You might have got me with that the first time ladies, but who me once
Can't get food again. It's basically what I'm saying. Yeah
Maybe he'll chase the booty
Oh really so much fun in the world delirious
Right, I know I think I'm only back you know
Yeah, I
Woke up for a little bit, but because you were supposed to have that reading
Right
What does I call me now, how do you know?
Call me now for your free reading
What's going on in the chat I want to read it and read you the chat what the chat
You're always writing the chats dick
No, I'm not we just pay attention to them because they're a part of this channel, too
Okay, well
That's not nice. That matters, but they're always mean and talking to always wins. Yeah, well, that's what chat does. I
Mean really ever can hit
Chat and chat wouldn't be with us with a panel, you know go ahead and I mean not really
Well, oh, maybe not, okay
Yeah, like we could still have a panel without the chat. I'm just saying. Oh
It goes to the clouds now
Yeah, that is my cheer I'm gonna go follow in the clouds. I'll see y'all later. Bye summer. I love you
Okay, bye. Thanks page by the way again. You're welcome, honey. You're welcome
Don't be run running out for them titties
If you see candy in the middle of the road somewhere don't fall for it
Well, and then there were two and then there were two
Psych are you going to bed because I'm gonna probably do the same thing, you know
You can't just run away
Need pre-bed pizza pre-bed pizza
Well, I hope you enjoy it
Bye-bye
Yeah, he does not into you my key. Who's my key?
It's my key is my oh my oh my key
Where every guy you go out you call it everybody's got wherever we go. I've got a call and everybody's got I don't know
Dave
We're gonna go get pizza or something. I don't know. It was being kind of
weirdos. Let's see, Rayden Demon is dead, he deleted the count, you won. Oh, come on,
Beta, that's not sure. Let's see, is that Michael Laguissimon? Oh, it's okay. I went
to bed, no, I was just lurking, I was lurking in that, like, fan of the opera in the backstage.
I have a little catacombs with that.
I have a water canal maze and a pipe organ. I like to
Ask and play it
Call for Christine
Christine Christine die
Did you love dance? I've got other fans. It's okay. Please. I love you page. Hopefully everyone's good
I'll stay for a little while longer from your chill sticks or something
A lot of people want to say it looks like people's it's slowing down. I guess
the other place to be
This is kind of
You know
You're pretty good lately because my house is looking better and stuff. I'm gonna get my bike fixed
I'll be I'll be happy as a clam happy that we stir
Yeah, so anyway
To say oh, you think you know so much you think you know so much with you my comment arm and says
You're you're sure for a bit arm and says
Someone's telling the arm is that sticky read my comments above
They don't see that you don't see Armin's a comment by Armin. I don't see one. I don't know if my eyesight going
Look it again. I don't see anything
Are you not seeing anything I started you stream right to them? I don't start so
and
I lose there I don't lose there
Yes, you remember the black guy from zoobly zoobly zoobly
I think his name is Ben Vereen right and Ben Vereen is like a famous actor
He's like a big smile. He has like the kind of Cheshire cat smile
I think he'd play the Cheshire cat in the Alice in Wonderland movie and
Yeah, he played some kind of weird line
There's like there's some weird animals in that show the weirdest one was like that
There's like a parrot lady. She had this with a parrot nose
Roots. Oh, you hold roots. You don't roots the uh mini series. Yeah, I watched that in place six grade. We watched
Laval person who was on you know reading rainbow and uh
What is blood money to use what is blood money to use a psyche, okay, so what is blood money to use it so
Are you saying what is it? What is it means to me? Hold on. What is blood money? Blood money is like, you know people
basically
Giving money for doing something very very bad
It says what about there's the blood money mean to me blood money mean people you know taking money to
You know on a live people and stuff like that on a live people or
You know horrible things right the most of the time if they are their
Okay, greetings. Lord Vader, how are you? I have to just close.
Okay, you're diamonds, children. Hold on, you wear diamonds. What are you talking about?
Oh, you're talking about the blood diamonds? Yeah, I guess if you have like, you know, child labor and
some African mines, you know, they're owned by one company.
All the diamond mines are owned by one South African company
and called DEB, ERS.
They have commercials about diamonds.
So some monopoly, it's basically, you know,
they own all the diamond mines,
so therefore they have a monopoly on the diamonds, right?
Hello, good morning, Vader.
How is everybody?
Hi, my tracks, my Mr. Tracy.
Hi. Hi, there's Trix. Oh, you're so happy. Have a good morning. Hi, Mr. Trix. Oh.
Hey, Jan. How are you? Hi, everybody. How's cat going? Listen, 1% of mine diamonds, yeah.
So it's like, yeah, very presentable, right? Okay, she's back. Hey, Paige.
The poems that you were reading to us that one time are those stories that were kind of like dark and funny and weird
Um, we'll remember we're with the limericks then I read that this book called um, like a
30 scary story what's it called it's right here. It's called uh, short it's called short and shivery
I don't know. I got this look at the child. I would use the scary stories are kind of dark stories and then
Otherwise, they're just for fairytales and eight stops fables. I think on the show, okay
It may have been a sub tables. Anyway, thank you. Okay
Problem, I don't know. Yeah, I have to I was reading some really cool stories. I you know
Should get back to reading some cool material. Hey, let's do random losers that around. Yeah, it's kind of Cal Canada. Yeah
You think leave Eric's feeling much better. It's like oh great. Oh leave Eric's in is your cat. Okay. Yeah, like Erickson
Yeah, we went on this chance cat leave Eric's in
the healing, you know
Let me sure
Kitty cats doing good. Yeah. He's doing good. Okay. I'm glad to hear that. We're all
We're all rooting for late leaf her life. Hey B. Hey B. I thought the real beta. I don't think it's a little beta
Do this hair is not so
purple
Okay
Everyone has invited your key power to your later. There's no pillabrate reading team. It's finally gone. Yeah
Well, no, he's I don't think he's gone. I think he's just no
Talking to diamond in private and that's fine
The cat's names. Oops. Yeah, I think your cat's name is uh, yeah, the cat's name is Lake Erickson
Lake Erickson had a little
Well, he's got a little scared, but you do you mean the breakfast are now good. Oh, you're happy. You're happy a trick
Just use happy you see you see something in the house. What are you looking at?
Are you happy? Oh, yeah, look my smile. So guys, I did give this really cool little kit page. Look I got
What's it called Timu you got this nail kit, you know, I was like, okay fine
You guys ever like it, you know clean your nails clean
So guys look I have all these tools now
How many tools are in there I just like a 50 piece set or something there's like a those like so many different
There's like one two. There's like three different nail clippers. There's a bottle opener. There's two pairs of scissors
There's a tweezers. There's a
Much of a ton of nail scrapers and stuff. So yeah
I think it's super funny. There's a bottle opener in there. I'm putting him a surprising
There's a wine opener because you get really fucking annoyed. Do you know what it sucks?
Fuck in your eyebrows. It hurts. Oh
And it's like a razor blade look at the girl. Oh shit. Oh, it's like a razor. It's a sharp. Oh my god
It's a little razor razor blade. Okay. Wow. That's dangerous. Okay
What else yeah, there's no there's like a little this is like a guess who's
Things are cuticles. I mean, it's like, you know, it's like so this feels really this feels like really light
But let's hear that play. I mean, it looks like it's not bad stuff. I mean
Pretty good deal guys. I guess take out team who came in a few days
Didn't take a long time to get here and it was really inexpensive
I think it was shipping and everything was like six or seven bucks. Hey boys and frog
He's eating his breakfast now big boy. It loves his groceries. Oh
Yeah, he's a beautiful cat. He's a gorgeous guy. Thank you. That's what's giving calluses, okay?
I'll I'll try to use I don't know. I'm afraid like you know
Remember everyone got that that there's a thing called a pet egg and I was like the little egg and it will collect the shaving
And you like it's yeah, I think it's cheese grater for your like corn for your feet
Yeah, and then I was like collected in the egg and then people would like
Do it like too much and then I would like her so it hurts so bad when you like scrape too much skin off
You know, I mean, they gotta be careful. It was like doing it that you know, you know, it's a lot manicurist. They uh
No
Hey, it's beauty motherfuckers
Yeah, he's fucking nose hairs heard 16 times worse than eyebrows or 10 times. Oh, I know I know
It's gotta be done. Yeah, there's nose hairs guys. You need a little like a little like a
Firmary, but yeah, I guess it's better to pluck than those hairs, but I'm happy to hear the news
Oh, come on, right region demons fine. I'm sure it is talking about
Yeah, absolutely fine. Not excessive. I think I you drink wine-saving you drink wine-saving. Okay
Yeah, like I drink this way said there's probably a beer opener and a wine opener in there because it's fucking not something
You don't want to drink while you're doing it like you just hit the paint is ridiculous
Yeah, I do have a a drink is a must
Yeah, I still have my like lemonade. I just drink one drink tonight. You're happy to hear the news you just
You
You get a little oopsie. Okay, sorry. Don't don't pee pee
Hey, I'm gonna say ignore the chat. The chat is just being silly. I mean really guys
Hey, hey everybody Mikey's here Jim poison frog dance chicken army. We're a page losers here
We're not a massive ordinance from Penetrator.
I think it's been ordinance, right?
Money for 20 was here, scum was here.
Wow, we had a great, we're having a great chat.
You know, if you can hit the like for me,
I'll probably stay for just a little while longer.
We're gonna have a nice day.
We're gonna have a nice intention for a day.
We're gonna be nice to somebody today.
We're gonna...
You know, we're gonna grant one of our own wishes today. We're gonna maybe help someone else grant
There's poison frog region demon related his main YouTube channel. I'm not sure. I'm not sure people are saying that I
Don't know if you leave it. It was lead
Why doesn't someone go look? I
Don't know. Yeah, I don't know if anyone I
Seen it
Sometimes channels will disappear. I'm love. You're a drink. You're drinking ice
Corona right now and empty an raging semen hot. Uh-huh. Meow
You're not the real beta stop it
Or private. Let me see
Btard
Made it in private. He might it might be private. He might have private
Count for the I don't know
He seems to be
He's gonna be happy. I wish him the best and you know, you know, unfortunately
sometimes
There can be some drama in relationships and you know people have falling outs, but I do wish everyone's the best
I'm not anybody
And oh, it's not the real beta. I could be midnight
Dating her. Oh, yeah, I thought that sounds I don't think that be the beat it wouldn't talk like that
I mean, maybe she would but she wouldn't
Have that
Psycho you can do a picture shoot and send the pictures to a modeling agency
I could and I also have these like in these AI modeling photos, you know, I'll set up
Look pretty good in them. It could be Kate. Oh, it can be Kate. Yeah, they don't know it is
People I like to hide in these
aliases
so
I was looking these old I have like over a thousand of these books and when the book I'm reading it
I said hey be a YouTube star. I've probably got a few years to go play. Yeah, and look
On my way
Show up with the AI you yeah, oh, so you know it was on tonight or really like guys if you you could hook me up with Danny
Or just our danger ranger. Do you even know danger ranger is he was very cute tonight? I don't know. He's I
Like his channel. He's very funny
Hey, I don't think he likes saints. Oh, that's kind of
Negative but
He
Very cute
Thanks to walk around shirt off a lot means the big big belly you guys know
Hey, okay, so you're celebrating with Mickey and me on me on show for the AI you somebody will pick you maybe
Somebody somebody I don't somebody someday. I think Chris K
I think there's like some hope with help there. We'll see what happens. Okay. Where are you Joker's left me?
Me me's there's left me in the dust
No, it doesn't look promising with Sentinel, God, or JT, or SIG, either, and so, yeah,
I choose you, Chris K. Let's do it.
What?
I'm kind of in love with Chris K. But if this guy, Danger Ranger, if somebody knows
him, I can offer you that, Chris K. I'll just go with Danger Ranger.
Oh my god, oh, yeah, I'm just on being greedy the pictures you showed us were
Great, I was I showed my family a family. Wow my kind of my mom and my
I think some of my mom's friends believe that those were real photos, you know, she's not shooting fun
They are like my sister is like, oh, we believe that for a second. My sister did quite believe that, you know
I forget guys, you know, also guys all the clothes in those photos. They you scroll down
They showed like the links to buy the clothes. And so that's a new way to kind of shop
It's the up close look on you
But yeah, a little bit too expensive for
For me to be considerate. I like to save I like to save money on clothes and stuff. You lose there
If anyone know this oh, yeah danger Danny
I'll get a danger would love to know you're interested in him
Yeah, I mean I chatted in his chat a little bit. I was like, hey, I'm in love with you
You know, I have a channel and he never responded to the chat really people in chat
And I think no one's chat. No, I was nobody knew I was kind of rare that nobody knew who I was but
You know, it is kind of like a peripheral community. I don't know
So yeah, there's denizen denizen's me. I got the cat the pizza, you know
You you go you go digital denizen
The loser Maya Maya, so yeah danger. Yeah, let danger know I am I'm interested
And if you come on the show, if anyone knows who you can come on the show to, do you research past looking at him?
Yeah, I mean, I know he doesn't like saying I mean, I've been following him for a while. I just like, you know
I saw he has some uh, you got uh, red pizza? Yeah, probably red.
Pre-bred, red pizza.
Pre-bred, okay. It's a pre-bred pizza.
I like a nice, I like a nice, I like a good cold cheese pizza.
Oh my god, we have to get him on your panel.
Yes, um, Maya, yes, seriously, I was, I want, yeah, I'm definitely,
if you can talk to Danger, because he doesn't know me in the chat.
you miss a part he uh oh i don't think he does he that's not a good but he looks like a very
sweet person i mean she's she seems like she loves them i think they seem like they love each other
i mean they fight a little bit i know i know some couples fight they seem like they love each other
though that's sad that's sad yeah but maybe i won't maybe i won't bother like he is married
Um, yeah, I'll finish the beer.
Can you guys just try to clean my nails a little bit?
Yeah, it sucks. I don't like when people are mean to their spouses,
but, you know, sometimes people fight and, you know, they make up
and I really don't like being in the middle of people's...
relationships and stuff. He's awful and yes, Loser is correct. He, oh, he, oh, I don't like to hear that.
Why are there all these accusations about people? I know that there is like, his dog was sick and
they ended up taking the doctor to the vet, you know. That's where, you know, I don't know
what happened though. Hopefully it wasn't anything.
That okay, it's the part where you okay, so he does it on the stream. I mean, I've never seen that
I mean, I haven't really watched that measure. He was in a good mood tonight
He's just getting attached to and like, you know, hang out with her
They're all happy and
I was saying maybe have you know, he's to kind of get drunk on streaming fight to and you know
Sometimes you'll fight when they drive those people have different relationships. I can't really judge
But you missed okay, so yeah, thank you for letting me know guys you guys are like my little birdies telling me
Tell me things to put me off to
Things I should know and I really do appreciate people who've been honest with me, too
And there's been a few of you look up the eight
Look at one of the eight prison story. It was the male doll with the male give birth
so
He was wife and the pop
Got wild with the pops and he killed. Okay. Well, that's four. I mean, it's a very sad story
A very sad story. Yeah, I don't know. I don't know. It's a terrible story and
I hear stuff about people and their dogs and other stuff.
I'm not sure if this is a veracity that it's upsetting,
you know, this kind of story is to get people in emotions,
and I just don't know,
so all the details all hold off judgment for the time being.
We have to get him, yeah, we have to get him on the panel.
So we'll see, hopefully everyone's,
you're gonna have a good day today.
Is there anything happening on YouTube?
It looks like a complete quiet day.
Quiet day on YouTube, let's see who's on.
Nobody, nobody's online, but it's all live.
No, it's rain sound.
Again, Oliver, oh my gosh, he looks like he's,
where's he sleeping?
He's okay.
Yeah, I mean, I think I just,
Don't know if he'll even come on the panel. I don't know if the guy seems to be find it all he's interested in characters
Into some questionable stuff, I do believe in kind of
People are you know changing and came in that way he says, uh, yeah a prison stage. Okay. Wow. Oh my gosh
That all of us there's a guy Oliver. He lives in Los Angeles. He's the kind of nerdy
That he's he's a YouTube streamer
And he's always going around the city alone.
And now he's doing a sleep stream and now wearing a shirt.
It's kind of funny.
OK.
I think that was weird.
What's weird?
Sleep streams.
Like, what the fuck, man?
Yeah.
Well, it's like, and I heard you're not
allowed to do them on like, you know, chatter bait,
for example, because some people have like this kind of.
Fantasy of a sleeping person. That's okay. I guess it's fine on YouTube, but yeah, he's he's been there
Knorr in a way
It's called. I think he's chat is called sleepstream, too
Yeah
Yeah, a little bit to see a little bit. It's a little bit disturbing, but
Oh, but I'm just saying like I couldn't I wouldn't trust myself to sleep and people watch me online
Like I probably like like everybody farts and everybody snores and everybody does weird shit
Yeah, I wake I wake up clipped be gay and proud. Yeah, I am gay and proud, you know, I'm just my same myself
I'm not even like I don't mean like gay is like, you know, I'm not even really
I'm not sexually active and so I don't
What I who knows
It's just now it's just creepy haunt
They were to donate to fuck with they want door donate to fuck with the person all night
Who are you talking about loser or look up the guy? Oh, yeah, okay, so you're talking about
danger
They were to donate to fuck with the person all night
Yeah, he does have like this kind of nephew, or I don't know if it's nephew or some friends
like this younger guy and they're just doing dares and getting each other with stun guns
and slapping each other.
I don't know.
It's just like he's kind of in a trailer park and there's people all high, it's kind of
funny.
I kind of enjoyed the show.
I haven't talked to Scribble in a little bit, it's kind of hard to give his attention.
There's benefits to having smaller chats that there's too big. It's really hard to
Keep up with them have conversations with them for
It's kind of you kind of like lose people in the crowd. Yeah. Yeah, and then it's like, you know, I'm surely
Panels will be off the chain when you know, I have like another probably 10 10 another 10 times more discovered
I have I have like about 25 55 or something like that 2500
But when I get to like 10,000, I think I will,
I think I'll have,
I think a lot of the subscribers will be people
that will actually come in the chat and stuff.
They used to be the best,
they don't know what to do,
the best streamer.
Yeah, I used to remember,
I remember this guy,
like a year ago,
he was like sleeping and he was like streaming,
like every day he was asleep.
And then he had his own setup.
So the super chats would come in
and like try to wake him up
and like get people watching them, watching him and stuff.
I wonder whatever happened to that guy.
Yeah, I meant the solution uses this deep join-out. Oh, okay. Yeah, I had a yeah
Yeah, they fuck with the streamer second you remember when Aldi called me sweetie. It was hilarious. Yeah, he called me sweetie
I mean it's like he was
You know, he says it's a little bit sweet on me
I don't know. I don't know these guys are playing hard to get some of them are
Kind of playing too easy to get I'm not sure Barbara. Thank you. I'm glad you have stayed live because you needed that reading
Oh awesome glad you got to talk to
to a pagey
Yeah, awesome. Yeah, so this is works okay to clean my nail. I mean it's like I
Do a clean and better, but yeah, it's a good little scraper just
Yeah, so yeah, I'm glad you know I'm glad people are enjoying the reading
great people coming in we had Bobby the other night from the
Raven Ravens tarot we have you know traveling tips you will stop by occasionally. We have of course page is awesome reader
be to the talented reader and
Well, there's oh
We have capricorn soul tribe and
And more we have we just have a lot of real. Yeah, a lot of readers here
So you're bound to get some insight into your question that will
Give some great assistance here. I think if you stick around the show you came here from positive vibes
Yeah, I mean too, but I'm trying to keep a positive bar, but sometimes it was hard with the panel
You know the panel can get a little bit
Routy sometimes, right?
For the most part they're good people and I read in the chats good people and
Really enjoying even if there's a little bit less people at times. I think it's kind of like a
Better feel and I think a quality of people and
Having fun guys. I love you guys. It's going good. Yeah room for positive vibes. Yep
Bedtime you got a hype from the light. Yeah when the sun comes up. I gotta I gotta crawl back in my coffin
You know I sleep in a
Sleeping in a in 16th century casket. No pretty comfortable
It's just uh, you know, I can't can't even the sunlight or I'll turn to ash
You saw you saw earlier
Just put a little bit of ash might be what time are you going eating breakfast? I don't know. Maybe I'll get it at
Six or seven, I think you'll get a bagel and stuff. I don't know if I'm hey, babe. Hey
Tracy. Oh, it's your tricks
Hi
Tricks smell so good. I noticed the cats smell so good dogs. They have kind of a dog smell the cats
I'd love their smell. I love their smell
What did they say they smell like that one time? You know, they smell like big marshmallows and like
Like the nurse knows so good. She's not a perfume or she ever she said that's like, you know
Like it's like beautiful sense to her. I mean sometimes you smell the mouth the mouth is kind of smell like fish, but
But that everything else is hey tricks
everything else is
nice
Hey, good night. Good night. Yep. Good night loser
Yep, yeah, I'll have a good sleep tonight guys, I know for today
Do it all over. I like I kind of like waking up in the afternoon. It's like hey, it's already time to time to party
But you know
I do like being a little bit more sober lately and I, you know, I'm trying to be better about not falling asleep on the panel, trying to get my house more organized.
A little bit surely guys, you know, we're making some progress. Hopefully you guys had fun today. I'll stand for another 13 minutes.
And I might let you guys go and, you know, enjoy your day and we'll be back on tonight, later tonight.
Hi, baby. You're my little babe. My little baby. I love cuddling with tricks. If I go under the covers
He just runs right in the car. He has some b-leg right there. And then if Lola's there
She'll start hissing and he tries to get under the covers too. She'll hiss and then he'll walk on top of us
He walks on top and sometimes she'll hiss more. Yeah
It's good on in a cat food and litter. Yeah good cat food and good
And the litter makes your cats smell good. Yep. These keys smell good
Hey, hey, goodbye. Bye Barbara later
Wish everyone a happy day, you know. Oh happy day. Oh happy. It's gonna seem Bible sauce
They just got a spirit written through me, right?
The spirit spirit of the spirit of the spirit of love
The father spirit
It's not a demon. It's not a demon. I'm not Emily Rose guys. I am
Some nice angel. Actually, you know, you can look up your birthday angel or there's like a bunch of angels corresponding to those demons in the Goetia.
And my angel is called Leelahel, L-E-L-A-H-E-L, Leelahel. They all have permission to do the last initials.
L. So her name is Lila hell kind of something little it's a little bit and she is the angel of dreams and
Prophecy and a lot of interesting things that I am actually interested in. It's kind of interesting how
Sometimes there's the
This kind of reading screen brings in the act inside and accuracy too. So, yeah
Bedtime got her back. Hi. Oh, it's okay losers going to bed
Barbara
is uh I'm going to bed soon yep I don't know I've been kind of sitting up a lot and my back
is kind of hurting I need a massage soon uh let's see and my link stands anybody any final words today
I want to make sure everyone is happy and everything is cool.
I want to thank everybody for participating in the chat.
We've had great chat today, great donation.
It's 62 degrees in Los Angeles, so wow.
Oh, OK.
And it's the air quality is a f***ing good.
Yeah, my battery might conk out too, so if it does.
Goodbye in advance. Yeah. I don't know. Yeah. So it looks like it got kind of quiet in chat. It is probably 9
Hey guys, there's a lot of places you can go and you guys, you know, you want to chill here and I love I love that
You guys are here. I love that
You have fun on the show. I hope to have a lot of great future content and
Exciting guys. I love you. I'm gonna go. Okay. Bye pagey. I'll see you later
Adios
Yeah
Kind of was rambling a little bit, right? It's okay. It's okay guys, but yeah, I love you guys, you know and
Everything will be a okay with me, right? I'll talk to you guys, yeah